Miracle Samson Ogunmola

Front end developer

CONTACT



miraclesamson16@gmai

I.com

Portfolio

miraclesamson.vercel

.app

SKILLS

Team collaboration User Interface Write programs Application monitoring research Application debugging

LANGUAGES

English

SUMMARY

Male | Nigeria, Ondo

Citizenship: Nigeria

Highly capable Front End Developer offering multilingual programming, system monitoring and maintenance prowess. Constantly automated build, deployment and integration processes, increasing team productivity 100%. Expert developer well-versed in Agile and Scrum methodologies. Effective collaborator and integrator translating technical terminology into easy-to-comprehend information.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Self employed

Jun 2018 - Jun 2021

- Created responsive websites from scratch.
- Design and development of various websites.
- Implementing complex front-end applications using dvnamic HTML.
- Support and development of new functionality for already existing projects.
- · Designing and maintaining front end for web and mobile applications.
- Maintaining websites for clients.

front end developer

Rou-Technology

Jan 2018 - Present

- Designed user-friendly software to improve accessibility and responsiveness.
- Used established coding standards to streamline debugging, documentation and system maintenance.
- Optimized websites to improve backward and crossbrowser compatibility.
- Collaborated with teammates to improve processes and ison produce better tools.

CERTIFICATIONS

Responsive Web design

solo learn

Dec 2021

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

BSC .ed

ADEYEMI COLLEGE OF EDUCATION

Apr 2014 - Sep 2019

REFERENCES

Olalekan Raheem

ROU Technology





raheemolalekanusman84@gmail.com